<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2210</PhotoLink><LastName>Aune</LastName><FirstName>Ashley</FirstName><DistrictNum>014</DistrictNum><Party>Democrat</Party><LeadershipPosition>Minority Floor Leader</LeadershipPosition><YearElected>2020</YearElected><YearsServed>5</YearsServed><Hometown>Kansas City</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>Platte</CountyName></County></Counties><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 204, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant>Michelle Brent</LegislativeAssistant><PhoneNumber>573-751-3618</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Ashley.Aune@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>Representative Ashley Aune, a Democrat, represents parts of Platte County (District 14) in the Missouri House of Representatives, including Kansas City, Weatherby Lake and Lake Waukomis.

Aune was elected to her first term in 2020 and re-elected in 2022 and 2024. After serving a term as Minority Whip, her Democratic colleagues elected her as House Minority Leader for the current General Assembly. She also serves as an ex-officio member of all House committees. During her first term in office, she was appointed by Gov. Mike Parson to the Missouri Military Preparedness and Enhancement Commission, where she worked with military and civilian leaders across the state to make Missouri the most welcoming place for active duty and retired military members and their families. She currently is co-chair of the Missouri Chamber of Commerce and Industry’s Technology Caucus.

Prior to politics, Representative Aune worked in marketing and owned her own agency. She received a bachelor’s degree in Communication Studies from the University of Kansas with a minor in English.

Born in Colorado and raised in Kansas, Aune now lives in the Kansas City Northland with her husband and stepdaughter.</Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1304</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies provisions relating to abortion</LongTitle><LRNumber>2712H.02I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1530</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Requires the levy and collection of a property tax for children's services in certain counties and cities</LongTitle><LRNumber>2936H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HCR</BillType><BillNumber>4</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Designates the last week in April each year as "Infertility Awareness Week"</LongTitle><LRNumber>1649H.02I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Murray, Marty Joe</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>078</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
