<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2075</PhotoLink><LastName>Patterson</LastName><FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName><DistrictNum>030</DistrictNum><Party>Republican</Party><LeadershipPosition>Speaker of the House</LeadershipPosition><YearElected>2018</YearElected><YearsServed>7</YearsServed><Hometown>Lees Summit</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>Jackson</CountyName></County></Counties><Committees><Committee><CommitteeName>Joint Committee on Capitol Security</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee></Committees><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 308, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant>Lisa Bondurant</LegislativeAssistant><PhoneNumber>573-751-0907</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Jonathan.Patterson@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>Dr. Jon Patterson, a Republican, represents District 30, which includes parts of Lee’s Summit. He was elected to his first two-year term in November of 2018.  Rep. Patterson currently serves as Speaker of the House.  

Rep. Patterson is a 1998 graduate of Blue Springs High School. He then attended the University of Missouri–Columbia, where he earned both his bachelor's and medical degree. After medical school, Dr. Patterson completed his surgical residency at Truman Medical Center in downtown Kansas City.  Dr. Patterson practiced general surgery in eastern Jackson County from 2011-2022.    

Rep. Patterson lives in Lee’s Summit with his wife, Jennifer. They have two children, Leah and Andrew. In his spare time, Dr. Patterson enjoys family time, reading, and golf. Dr. Patterson is committed to public service through medical missions. He has completed surgical mission trips around the world, including to the Dominican Republic, Jamaica, and Jordan.

</Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>746</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Provides protections against discrimination and antisemitism in public schools and public postsecondary educational institutions</LongTitle><LRNumber>1725H.02I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1542</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Allows the department of economic development to publish on its website the required annual reports on revenue bond issuances and general obligation bond issuances submitted to the department by municipalities</LongTitle><LRNumber>3194H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>100</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Modifies provisions relating to income tax</LongTitle><LRNumber>0158H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Davidson, Bishop</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>130</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HJR</BillType><BillNumber>1</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Proposes a constitutional amendment to impose an appropriation spending limitation and to establish the "Tax Reform Fund" to be used to fund budgetary shortfalls, subject to an appropriation limitation, implement sales tax changes, and allow for certain taxation changes based on revenue triggers, by general law</LongTitle><LRNumber>1138H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Davidson, Bishop</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>130</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
