<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2095</PhotoLink><LastName>Wright</LastName><FirstName>Dale</FirstName><DistrictNum>116</DistrictNum><Party>Republican</Party><YearElected>2018</YearElected><YearsServed>7</YearsServed><Hometown>Farmington</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>Madison</CountyName></County><County><CountyName>St. Francois</CountyName></County></Counties><Committees><Committee><CommitteeName>Elections</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Higher Education and Workforce Development</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Ways and Means</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee></Committees><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 115-A, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant>Nancy Suthoff</LegislativeAssistant><PhoneNumber>573-751-3455</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Dale.Wright@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>Representative Dale Wright, a Republican, represents portions of St. Francois and Madison Counties (District 116) in the Missouri House of Representatives. He was elected to his first two-year term in November 2018.

In addition to his legislative duties, Wright is a healthcare executive, past business owner, and partner of the Actalur Group, LLC, a healthcare consulting company, and Angle Medical Solutions, a pharmaceutical and medical device distributor. During his 47 years in the industry, he received the Rising Star Award from Cardinal Healthcare, Manager of the Year from Health Services Corporation of America, and National Healthcare Executive of the Year from Allegiance Healthcare. Wright was also named to the Who’s Who of American Healthcare Executives. Most recently, he was named the 2023 “Distinguished Alumni” at his alma mater, Mineral Area College.  

Representative Wright has been a member of the Farmington City Council, the MCII Sheltered Workshop Board, the Mineral Area College Foundation Board, the Missouri Hospital Association’s Purchasing Council Board and the Farmington Police Personnel Board. He has volunteered with the Boy Scouts of America, the PTA, Big Brothers, and The American Heart Association.

He is a graduate of Farmington High School and he graduated from the Mineral Area College in 1973 with an ABA.

Born in St. Louis, Representative Wright was raised in Farmington where he currently resides with his wife, Denise. They have three children, Andrea, Aaron, and Stephanie, eleven grandchildren, and five great grandchildren. They attend The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints.
</Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>330</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies provisions relating to certain local taxes</LongTitle><LRNumber>0409H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>474</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Creates provisions relating to payments for prescription drugs</LongTitle><LRNumber>1376H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1591</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Increases the cigarette tax from $0.17 per pack of 20 cigarettes to $0.37 per pack or an amount equal to the lowest tax levied by any other state, whichever is less, upon voter approval</LongTitle><LRNumber>3099H.02I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredAmendment><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>37</BillNumber><LegislationType>Amendment</LegislationType><LRNumber>0232H01.43H</LRNumber><AmendmentStatus>Distributed</AmendmentStatus><AmdDescription/></SponsoredAmendment><SponsoredAmendment><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>107</BillNumber><LegislationType>Amendment</LegislationType><LRNumber>0740H02.23H</LRNumber><AmendmentStatus>Distributed</AmendmentStatus><AmdDescription/></SponsoredAmendment></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
