<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2508</PhotoLink><LastName>Steinmetz</LastName><FirstName>Connie</FirstName><DistrictNum>087</DistrictNum><Party>Democrat</Party><YearElected>2024</YearElected><YearsServed>1</YearsServed><Hometown>Maryland Heights</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>St. Louis</CountyName></County></Counties><Committees><Committee><CommitteeName>Children and Families</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Elementary and Secondary Education</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Pensions</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee></Committees><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 135-BC, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant>Terrence Fiala</LegislativeAssistant><PhoneNumber>573-751-0100</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Connie.Steinmetz@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>Representative Connie Steinmetz, a Democrat, proudly represents part of St. Louis County (District 87) in the Missouri House of Representatives. She was elected to her first two-year term in November 2024.

A lifelong advocate for education, Steinmetz dedicated nearly 40 years to teaching kindergarten, first, and second grades in the Clayton and Hazelwood school districts. Her career as an educator was marked by a passion for nurturing young minds and fostering a love of learning, values she continues to uphold in her legislative work.

Steinmetz follows in the footsteps of her late father, Charles (Jack) Callahan, a union member and leader, as well as her mother-in-law, Kaye Steinmetz, who served with distinction in the Missouri House of Representatives for 18 years. This family legacy of public service inspires her commitment to addressing the needs of her constituents and working to improve the quality of life for families in her district.

An active member of her community, Steinmetz served as President for the HNEA - a teacher union in Hazelwood, and is involved in the Kiwanis Club, where she contributes to initiatives that support children and local families. She values community engagement and is dedicated to creating opportunities that benefit her district’s residents.

Steinmetz is the proud mother of three daughters: Nancy, Sarah, and Rachel. She cherishes the time spent with her family and draws strength and inspiration from them as she works to make a difference for Missouri families.
   </Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>184</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Requires a notice of intent to excavate to the department of natural resources to check whether the excavation is in a site contaminated with hazardous waste</LongTitle><LRNumber>1364H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Clemens, Doug</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>072</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>306</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Requires public school districts and charter schools to prevent student use of electronic personal communications devices during regularly scheduled instructional activities</LongTitle><LRNumber>1350H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Steinhoff, Kathy</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>045</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>487</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Creates provisions relating to insurance coverage for fertility treatments</LongTitle><LRNumber>1242H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Appelbaum, LaDonna</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>071</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>844</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Establishes provisions governing health and safety measures in public schools</LongTitle><LRNumber>2086H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Hruza, George</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>089</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>917</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Requires insurance coverage of skin cancer screenings</LongTitle><LRNumber>2091H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Hruza, George</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>089</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HCR</BillType><BillNumber>4</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Designates the last week in April each year as "Infertility Awareness Week"</LongTitle><LRNumber>1649H.02I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Murray, Marty Joe</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>078</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill><CoSponsoredBill><BillType>HJR</BillType><BillNumber>6</BillNumber><LegislativeType>Co-sponsor</LegislativeType><LongTitle>Proposes a constitutional amendment relating to property tax exemptions</LongTitle><LRNumber>0517H.01I</LRNumber><BillSponsor>Griffith, Dave</BillSponsor><SponsorDistrict>060</SponsorDistrict></CoSponsoredBill></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
