<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2502</PhotoLink><LastName>Mosley</LastName><FirstName>Chanel</FirstName><DistrictNum>075</DistrictNum><Party>Democrat</Party><YearElected>2024</YearElected><YearsServed>1</YearsServed><Hometown>Black Jack</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>St. Louis</CountyName></County></Counties><Committees><Committee><CommitteeName>Consent and Procedure</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Ways and Means</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Special Committee on Intergovernmental Affairs</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee></Committees><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 105-I, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant>Kendrick Henry</LegislativeAssistant><PhoneNumber>573-751-5538</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Chanel.Mosley@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>Representative Chanel Mosley, a Democrat, represents St. Louis (District 75) in the Missouri House of Representatives. She was elected to her first two-year term in November 2024.

Born and raised in the City of St. Louis, Mosley is the daughter of former State Representative Jay Mosley and State Senator Angela Mosley. She graduated from McCluer High School in Florissant, Missouri, where she now resides with her husband and children.

In the legislature, Representative Mosley is focused on strengthening education, particularly improving student attendance and addressing emotional distress among youth. She advocates for equipping educators with the tools they need to support students facing significant stress, especially those lacking emotional support at home.

Mosley is also a vocal advocate against gun violence, working to address rising homicide rates and the displacement of families impacted by violent crime. Additionally, she is committed to raising awareness and finding solutions for the crisis of missing and murdered African American women and girls.
</Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1096</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Creates the "Missing and Murdered African American Women and Girls Task Force"</LongTitle><LRNumber>2204H.02I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1432</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Requires teacher education programs to provide credit hours and licensed teachers to participate in professional development regarding social and emotional learning and in social work</LongTitle><LRNumber>2288H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1433</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Creates provisions relating to insurance coverage of additional living expenses due to gun violence</LongTitle><LRNumber>2250H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1434</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies provisions governing absences from school</LongTitle><LRNumber>2243H.02I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
