<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2076</PhotoLink><LastName>Haden</LastName><FirstName>Kent</FirstName><DistrictNum>043</DistrictNum><Party>Republican</Party><YearElected>2018</YearElected><YearsServed>7</YearsServed><Hometown>Mexico</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>Audrain</CountyName></County><County><CountyName>Callaway</CountyName></County><County><CountyName>Monroe</CountyName></County></Counties><Committees><Committee><CommitteeName>Health and Mental Health</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Vice-Chair</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Administration and Accounts</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Agriculture</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Special Committee on Rural Issues</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee></Committees><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 311, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant>Dylan Robinson</LegislativeAssistant><PhoneNumber>573-751-3649</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Kent.Haden@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>Rep. Kent Haden, a Republican, represents Audrain and Callaway Counties (District 43) in the Missouri House of Representatives. He was elected to his first two-year term in November 2018.

Prior to his legislative duties, Haden worked for eight years for the Missouri Department of Agriculture as the state epidemiologist. Haden has also worked in private veterinary practice and as a disease control veterinarian for Missouri. He also worked for 28 years for MFA, Incorporated, last serving as vice president in charge of feed and animal health.

Haden is a member of the Missouri Pork Producers, American Quarter Horse Association, the Mexico Chamber of Commerce, and Missouri Farm Bureau. He has been named the American Feed Industry’s Man of the Year and the National Cattlemen’s Regional Innovation winner.

Haden is a 1969 graduate of North Callaway High School. He graduated from the University of Missouri in 1973 before going on to veterinary school, where he graduated in 1976.

Born in Fulton, Haden currently resides in Mexico with his wife, Brenda. They have three children: Brent, Tyler, and Jennifer. Haden is a member of First Baptist Church of Mexico, where he teaches Sunday school, and is currently chairman of the deacons. 
</Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>439</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Creates provisions relating to dental plans</LongTitle><LRNumber>0991H.02I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>440</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies and creates new provisions relating to utilities</LongTitle><LRNumber>1325H.04C</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1116</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Allows real property owners building a fence to enter an adjoining property up to ten feet without liability for trespassing</LongTitle><LRNumber>1091H.03P</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1404</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies provisions relating to birthing centers</LongTitle><LRNumber>2990H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
