<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2248</PhotoLink><LastName>Walsh Moore</LastName><FirstName>Bridget</FirstName><DistrictNum>093</DistrictNum><Party>Democrat</Party><LeadershipPosition>Minority Caucus Policy Chair</LeadershipPosition><YearElected>2020</YearElected><YearsServed>5</YearsServed><Hometown>St. Louis</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>St. Louis</CountyName></County></Counties><Committees><Committee><CommitteeName>Local Government</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Ranking Minority Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Special Committee on Intergovernmental Affairs</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Ranking Minority Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Conservation and Natural Resources</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee></Committees><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 105-D, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant/><PhoneNumber>573-751-0211</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Bridget.Walshmoore@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>State Representative Bridget Walsh Moore, a Democrat, represents parts of South St. Louis County (District 93) in the Missouri House of Representatives, which includes parts of the neighborhoods and townships of Lemay, Mehlville, Affton, and Bella Villa. She was elected to her first two-year term in November 2020.

Walsh Moore is a lifelong St. Louisan. She grew up in Kirkwood and graduated from Ursuline Academy. At Bradley University, she studied Arabic and International Relations and spent one semester at The American University in Cairo, Egypt, immersing herself in one of the world's largest cities and its role as a trade hub between Africa, Asia, and Europe. She graduated as a member of the International Relations Honor Society and later earned her Chancellor’s Certificate in International Trade from the World Trade Center through a joint program with the University of Missouri–St. Louis. 

Walsh Moore worked in manufacturing and became a founding member of the North Broadway Business Development Association. She later worked as a customs brokerage agent, where she navigated the steel tariffs and import legalities of Chinese products during the beginning of the COVID-19 outbreak. She also created and managed several foreign trade zones for major Missouri companies.

Walsh Moore is a proud member of the St. Louis Metropolitan St. Patrick’s Day Parade, an organization that was founded in part by her grandparents. She is the founder and Co-Chair of the American Irish State Legislators Caucus. In 2023, she was invited to address the Irish Parliament in her role with the organization.

Walsh Moore plays an active role in several community organizations, including the Great Rivers Environmental Law Center, the North Broadway Business Development Community, the Disabled Athletes Sports Association, and the Progressive Democrats of Lemay. Additionally, she serves as co-chair of the Sportsman's Caucus in the Missouri House. 

Walsh Moore lives in South St. Louis County with her husband, Greg Moore, and the couple welcomed their first child in 2021. She is also a proud cancer survivor.

</Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1184</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies provisions relating to tort actions based on improper health care</LongTitle><LRNumber>2508H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1563</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Creates the "Missouri Earned Family and Medical Leave Act"</LongTitle><LRNumber>2489H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HCR</BillType><BillNumber>19</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Recognizes and celebrates the special relationship between the United States and Ireland</LongTitle><LRNumber>3001H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HCR</BillType><BillNumber>20</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Designates July 11, 2025 as Srebrenica Genocide Remembrance Day in Missouri</LongTitle><LRNumber>2999H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HR</BillType><BillNumber>491</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Urges the state to address and support the needs of the state's most vulnerable citizens in response to the report on mental health care released by the Department of Justice</LongTitle><LRNumber>2789H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredAmendment><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>437</BillNumber><LegislationType>Amendment</LegislationType><LRNumber>1524H01.02H</LRNumber><AmendmentStatus>Distributed</AmendmentStatus><AmdDescription/></SponsoredAmendment><SponsoredAmendment><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>497</BillNumber><LegislationType>Amendment</LegislationType><LRNumber>0786H02.07H</LRNumber><AmendmentStatus>Distributed</AmendmentStatus><AmdDescription/></SponsoredAmendment><SponsoredAmendment><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1464</BillNumber><LegislationType>Amendment</LegislationType><LRNumber>3110H02.11H</LRNumber><AmendmentStatus>Adopted</AmendmentStatus><AmdDescription>HA 3</AmdDescription></SponsoredAmendment><SponsoredAmendment><BillType>SB</BillType><BillNumber>160</BillNumber><LegislationType>Amendment</LegislationType><LRNumber>1382H04.04H</LRNumber><AmendmentStatus>Point of Order</AmendmentStatus><AmdDescription>HA 11</AmdDescription></SponsoredAmendment></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
