<ROOT><RepresentativeData><RepresentativeInfo><PhotoLink>https://images.house.mo.gov/MemberPhoto.aspx?id=2489</PhotoLink><LastName>Jacobs</LastName><FirstName>Martin</FirstName><DistrictNum>038</DistrictNum><Party>Democrat</Party><YearElected>2024</YearElected><YearsServed>1</YearsServed><Hometown>Liberty</Hometown><Counties><County><CountyName>Clay</CountyName></County></Counties><Committees><Committee><CommitteeName>Economic Development</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Elementary and Secondary Education</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee><Committee><CommitteeName>Pensions</CommitteeName><CommitteePosition>Member</CommitteePosition></Committee></Committees><CapitolAddress>MO House of Representatives, 201 West Capitol Avenue, Room 101-H, Jefferson City MO 65101</CapitolAddress><LegislativeAssistant>Katie Lee</LegislativeAssistant><PhoneNumber>573-751-2238</PhoneNumber><EmailAddress>Martin.Jacobs@house.mo.gov</EmailAddress><Biography>Representative Martin Jacobs, a Democrat, represents part of Clay County (District 38) in the Missouri House of Representatives. He was elected to his first two-year term in November 2024.

Rep. Jacobs earned his bachelor’s degree in history from Gustavus Adolphus College and a doctorate in education from the University of Missouri in 1992. He dedicated 44 years of his career to education, serving as a teacher, assistant principal, principal, and coach in Nebraska before coaching, and serving as a principal at Liberty High School and Liberty North High School, here in Missouri. 

He also spent four years as an Adjunct Professor. Throughout his distinguished career, Rep. Jacobs received numerous accolades, including being named Administrator of the Year in 2019 by the Missouri Interscholastic Press Association.

In addition to his legislative duties, Rep. Jacobs is an active member of the Kiwanis Club of Liberty and attends First Presbyterian Church in Independence. He is the proud father of two children and brings his deep commitment to education and public service to his work in the Missouri House.
   </Biography></RepresentativeInfo><RepresentativeLegislation><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1196</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies the "Senior Citizen Property Tax Relief Credit" or "circuit breaker" tax credit by modifying the eligibility criteria, increasing the maximum upper limit, and increasing the property tax credit amounts</LongTitle><LRNumber>2344H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HB</BillType><BillNumber>1365</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Modifies provisions governing school administrator evaluations and contracts</LongTitle><LRNumber>2784H.02C</LRNumber></SponsoredBill><SponsoredBill><BillType>HJR</BillType><BillNumber>71</BillNumber><LegislationType>Sponsor</LegislationType><LongTitle>Proposes a constitutional amendment relating to the election and duties of sheriffs and the funding for sheriff's offices </LongTitle><LRNumber>2356H.01I</LRNumber></SponsoredBill></RepresentativeLegislation></RepresentativeData></ROOT>
